Gal Zisin

Full Stack developer with 2 years of hands-on experience developing a variety of applications on both the server and client sides. Using Node.js, .NET C#, JAVA, MongoDB, MS SQL on the backend and React.js, Angular 2+, JavaScript on the front-end. Knowledge and use of Design Patterns.

Phone: 0508138257

Email: galzisin86@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/GalZisin

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/gal-

zisin-907b65b0/

Portfolio:

https://gal-zisin- portfolio.herokuapp.com/

EXPERIENCE

CodeValue, Herzliya — Full-Stack Developer

2021 - PRESENT

 Development of Zoomd's SaaS platfrom. Using Angular9, ngzorro library, node.js. Manage versions using GIT in Azure DevOps environment.

Ladpc New Automation, Haifa — Full-Stack Developer

2020 - 2021

- Development and maintenance of ERP system in department of salary and human resources.
- Using JAVA 8 JSP pages, Oracle DB 19c. Perl scripts, Putty (Linux).
- Manage versions using TFS.

Yalo Star Holdings, Omer — Full-Stack Developer

2020 - 2020

- Development of a tourism app.
- .NET C# back-end, Web Scraping with html agility pack.

Navon-Azran, Tel Aviv — *Electrical Engineer*

2016 - 2018

 Designing and drawing electrical infrastructure of Data centers in MED-1 facilities.

ABB Technologies, Haifa — Electrical Engineer

2014 - 2016

• Commissioning engineer. Calibrations and testing of protection relays.

EDUCATION

HackerU, Ramat Gan — Full-Stack Developer

2018 - 2020

Ariel University, Ariel -B.Sc. in Electrical Engineering

2009 - 2014

SKILLS

HTML

CSS & SASS

JavaScript

TypeScript

React.js

Angular 2+

REST API

Bootstrap

Material Ui

Redux

Node.js

Express

Mongo

Mongoose

Swagger

.NET C# WPF

JAVA

MSSQL

My-SQL

Oracle

TFS

GitHub

Military service

2005 - 2008

Artillery corps

Languages

English - high level

Hebrew - native

Russian - native